

LISANDRO BIGI

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Hello! I'm from Córdoba, Argentina, and I'm a Front End Developer and an Anthropologist.

I have professional experience working in projects with: React | Vue.js | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | TypeScript | Git | Node.js | Wordpress. I also have an advanced English level.

I'm interested in Front-end, Web Development, Responsive Web Design, User Interfaces (UI), User Experience (UX), Web3, APIs, Full-Stack and Web Design.

CONTACT

+54 9 351 631 9690



bigilisandro@gmail.com



Córdoba, Argentina

SKILLS



















EXPERIENCE

INCLUIT, React Developer

JUN 2022 - PRESENT

Currently working for iDocket company in the development of a UCMS software platform. Using React for the front-end development.

KICKSTA, Front-end Developer

MAY 2021 - JUN 2022

I worked for this US company in their own main products using Vue.js and JavaScript in general.

PENGYI LABS, Front-end Developer

JUN 2019 - JUL 2021

I worked for a software development company with projects in Vue.is and React for clients all around the world. Also working with Node.js and Wordpress.

EDUCATION

EDUCATIONIT, Blockchain Ethereum Solidity MAY 2022 - AGO 2022

VUE MASTERY, Vue.js Learning Platform DEC 2020 - DEC 2021

CODERHOUSE, React.js

FEB 2020 - JUN 2020

ACAMICA, Full Stack Web Development NOV 2019 - JUN 2020

CODERHOUSE, UX/UI Design

MAY 2020 - SEP 2020

FFyH - UNC, Anthropology Degree

FEB 2013 - MAR 2020

CODERHOUSE. Web Designer

OCT 2019 - DIC 2019



